Edwin J. Feulner Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Heritage Foundation, 1953-2013 (Box 138-517)
  - President's Essays
    - Undated, (1 folder) (Box 482)
  - President's office files
    - Blackburn, Benjamin B., trustee, 1974-1976
    - Budget, 1973-1977, undated
    - Congratulatory correspondence on appointment of Feulner as president, 1977
    - Consortium file, 1979, undated
    - De Nauw, Lois, paintings on display at Heritage Foundation, 1977-1983
    - Freedoms Foundation Award, 1977-1978, (2 folders)
    - Heritage Foundation history, 1973-1983
    - Insurance, 1977-1981, undated
    - Memoranda (Box 483)
      - James, Jerry P., 1974-1975
      - Weyrich, Paul M., 1971-1976
    - Memoranda to the files, 1977-2000, 2010, undated, (2 folders)
    - Monthly president's letter, 1977-1980
    - National Security Record, 1979-1982
    - Receipts, 1979
      - Leon Office Machines
      - Miscellaneous
      - Pete Lambdon & Sons
    - Red Fox meetings
      - Middleburg, Va., 1972, Mar. 23
      - Frederick, Md., 1972, Dec. 5-6
      - Dulles, Va., 1974, Dec. 6-7
      - Baltimore, Md., 1976, Mar. 6-7
      - Annapolis, Md., 1978, July 14-15
      - Richmond, Va., 1979, July 27-28 (Box 484)
      - Annapolis, Md., 1980, Aug. 7-8
      - Fredericksburg, Va., 1981, Aug. 7-8
      - Unknown, 1983
    - Research Advisory Panel, 1976-1977, undated
    - Rosenthal, Benjamin S., investigation of grassroots lobbying, 1977-1978
    - Saunders, Thomas H., 1978
    - Third Annual Freedom Conference, Valley Forge, Pa., postponed, 1979
    - Zimbabwe/Rhodesia, 1977
  - President's Private Sector Survey on Cost (Grace Commission)
    - 1981
    - 1982, (3 folders); (2 folders) (Box 485)
    - Undated
  - Public interest legal foundations, survey, 1986-1987, undated, (2 folders)
  - Public Relations Department, 1977-1996, undated, (2 folders)
  - Publications Department
    - Miscellany, 1975, 1994-1997, 2003, 2011, undated
    - Mockups, 1977-1978, 1986, 1992, undated
    - Publications index, 1989-1995 (Box 486)
    - Sales reports, 1985-1993, (2 folders)
  - Reading file, 1975, July-Aug., (5 folders)
  - Reagan, Ronald
    - Chair in public policy at Heritage Foundation, 1988-1990
    - Transition team members paid through Heritage Foundation, 1980-1981, undated
  - Recommendations
    - Administrations, presidential
      - 1980-1981, (3 folders)
      - 1982-1992, undated, (7 folders) (Box 487)
    - General
      - 1974-1986, (2 folders)
      - 1987-1997, (2 folders) (Box 488)
  - Reports
    - Annual
      - 1980-1997, (3 folders)
      - 1998-2013, (3 folders) (Box 489)
    - Quarterly
      - 1973-1982, (4 folders)
      - 1983-1987, (7 folders) (Box 490)
      - 1988-1990, (6 folders) (Box 491)
      - 1991, (1 folder) (Box 492)
      - 1992-1994, (6 folders)
      - 1995-1997, (6 folders) (Box 493)
      - 1998-2000, (6 folders) (Box 494)
      - 2001-2004, (6 folders) (Box 495)
      - 2005, (1 folder) (Box 496)
      - 2006-2012, (7 folders)
    - Weekly (Box 497)
      - 1977-1979, 1996-2005, (7 folders)
      - 2006, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 498)
      - 2008-2010, (4 folders)
  - Research Department
    - General
      - 1977-1986, (2 folders)
      - 1987-1996, (2 folders) (Box 499)
    - Vice president, 1979-1995
  - Resource Bank
    - General, 1977-1998, undated, (2 folders)
    - Meetings
      - Chicago, Ill., 1981-1986, 1992-1996, 2004, (6 folders)
      - Dallas, Tex., 2011
      - Los Angeles, Calif., 1979, 2009, (2 folders)
      - Miami, Fla., 2010
      - Oak Brook, Ill., 1998
      - Philadelphia, Pa.
        - 1997
        - 1999-2007, (4 folders) (Box 500)
      - Sacramento, Calif., 1995
      - San Diego, Calif., 1987
  - Resources for freshmen congressmen, 1972-1978, undated, (2 folders)
  - Résumés, 1983, 1996-2000, 2010-2011, undated
  - Robert Russell & Associates
    - Marketing survey, 1988, (2 folders)
    - Memoranda
      - 1982-1986
      - 1987-1991, 1997-1998, (5 folders) (Box 501)
  - Samuel Roberts Noble Foundation
    - 1973-1978, (5 folders)
    - 1979-1986, (8 folders) (Box 502)
    - 2010 (Box 503)
  - Scaife Family Charitable Trust
    - 1974-1981, (10 folders)
    - 1982-1983, (3 folders) (Box 504)
  - Seabrook Nuclear Power Plant Project, 1976-1978, undated
  - Sejong Institute, Seoul (Korea), 1991
  - Seminars, 1976-1978, 2001, 2011, undated
  - Senate Steering Committee, 1976-1980, undated
  - Seoul Peace Prize Cultural Foundation, Peace Prize Committee, 1996, 2006-2012, (4 folders)
  - Six-Pak meetings, 1979, 1983, 1993-1997, (3 folders)
  - Smith Richardson Foundation
    - 1975-1977
    - 1978-1990, (4 folders) (Box 505)
  - South Africa Project, 1976
  - Special Projects Office
    - Candidates for government positions, 1980, (2 folders)
    - Presidential leadership, 1980-1985, undated
    - Smith, Barbara J.
      - 1977-1978
      - 1979-1980, (3 folders) (Box 506)
    - Washington Briefing Series, 1977, undated
    - Washington Semester Program, 1978
  - Staff handbook, 1979-1980
  - Staff listings, 1977, undated
  - Staff skills survey results, 2005
  - Stanton Group, 1980 See also Containers 138-144, administrative memoranda
  - Statewide Railroad Planning for New Hampshire: Analysis of Socio-Economic Factors, 1975
  - Strategic Arms Limitation Talks, 1979, undated
  - Studies completed, 1995-1997
  - Survey magazine, 1982-1990, undated, (2 folders) (Box 507)
  - Swartz & Associates, 1995, undated
  - Terrorism, 1978-1979
  - Testimonial/congratulatory/thank-you letters
    - 1972-1991, (5 folders)
    - 1992-1999, 2007-2012, undated, (5 folders) (Box 508)
  - Think Tank Group meeting, Washington, D.C., 1993, Aug. 19
  - "Today at Heritage...", 1992-1999
  - Town Hall
    - 1992-1993, (3 folders)
    - 1994-2005, 2011, (5 folders) (Box 509)
  - "Truth in Testimony" rule, 1996-1997
  - Unidentified draft, 1995
  - Union League Strategy Group, 1990-1992, undated, (2 folders)
  - United Nations Assessment Project See Containers 504-505, Smith Richardson Foundation
  - United States-Japan Foundation, 1982 (Box 510)
  - United States Industrial Council, 1977-1983
  - Vice presidency, 1974
  - Videotape Project, 1997
  - Wall Street Journal, investigation by and interview, 1991-1995, undated, (2 folders)
  - Walter Lippman Colloquium of 1938, 1997, (2 folders)
  - Washington International Studies Council, 1992-1998, 2005-2007
  - Weekly confidential calendars
    - circa 1987, 1993
    - 1994-1996, (5 folders) (Box 511)
    - 1997-2000, (5 folders) (Box 512)
    - 2001, (1 folder) (Box 513)
    - 2002-2004, (5 folders)
    - 2005-2006, (4 folders) (Box 514)
    - 2007, (1 folder) (Box 515)
    - 2008-2009, (4 folders)
    - 2010-2011, (5 folders) (Box 516)
    - 2012-2013, (2 folders) (Box 517)
  - Williams, Hosea, 1967-1982
  - WorldWide Parking, 1996
  - Y. C. Wang Project, 1988-1991
- Organizations, 1957-2014 (Box 517-742)
  Meeting minutes and related material, reports, correspondence, memoranda, notes, financial records, legal records, printed matter, and other papers pertaining to Feulner's membership in various organizations, boards, commissions, committees, and clubs outside of the Heritage Foundation.
  Arranged alphabetically by name of organization.
  - Acton Institute (Box 517)
    - 1994-1998, (5 folders)
    - 1999-2011, (6 folders) (Box 518)
  - Adam Smith Institute
    - 1976-1977, (2 folders)
    - 1978-1990, (2 folders) (Box 519)
  - Aequus Institute
    - Board meetings
      - 1989-1991, (6 folders)
      - 1992, (6 folders); (1 folder) (Box 520, Box 521)
      - 1993, (6 folders); (1 folder) (Box 522)
      - 1994, (5 folders)
      - 1995, (1 folder); (6 folders) (Box 523)
      - 1996, (1 folder); (7 folders) (Box 524)
      - 1997, (1 folder); (5 folders) (Box 525)
      - 1998, (2 folders); (3 folders) (Box 526)
      - 1999, (3 folders) (Box 527)
      - 2000, (4 folders)
      - 2001-2002, (6 folders) (Box 528)
      - 2003-2004, (7 folders) (Box 529)
      - 2006, (1 folder) (Box 530)
      - 2008-2011, (6 folders)
      - 2013 (Box 531)
    - General
      - 1985-1988, (6 folders)
      - 1989-1990, (6 folders) (Box 532)
      - 1991, (1 folder) (Box 533)
      - 1992-1998, (7 folders)
      - 1999-2006, (7 folders) (Box 534)
      - 2007-2012, (3 folders) (Box 535)
  - Alpha Kappa Psi
    - Chairman's Advisory Council, 2006-2008, (2 folders)
    - Conferences and conventions
      - Eastern Region Convention, Buffalo, N.Y., 1969
      - Mideast Regional Conference
        - Norfolk, Va., 1967
        - Blacksburg, Va., 1968
        - Chapel Hill, N. C., 1969
      - National Convention (Box 536)
        - Orlando, Fla., 1968, (2 folders)
        - Las Vegas, Nev., 1971, (2 folders)
      - Southeastern Regional Convention, Atlanta, Ga., 1969
    - Constitution Committee
      - 1965-1968, (4 folders)
      - 1978-1982 (Box 537)
    - District director files
      - Correspondence and memoranda, 1965-1967
      - Kirkman, Arthur, 1966-1967
      - Old Dominion University, Norfolk, Va., 1965-1967
      - University of Richmond, Richmond, Va., 1965-1967
      - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, Blacksburg, Va., 1965-1967
    - Executive Committee
      - 1977, (2 folders)
      - 1978-1980, (3 folders) (Box 538)
    - General, 1965-1974, 1986, undated, (6 folders)
    - Miscellany
      - Efficiency ratings, 1964-1969
      - Legal case, In re L. G. Balfour Co., 1967, (2 folders) (Box 539)
      - Newsletters and bulletins, 1965-1970, (2 folders)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1967-1969
      - Printed matter, circa 1966-1969, 2006, 2012
    - Regional director files
      - Alumni, 1967-1970
      - Chapter financial records, 1967-1970
      - District directors, 1968-1970
      - East Carolina University, Greenville, N.C., 1966-1969
      - Fraternity expansion, 1966-1969
      - George Washington University, Washington, D.C., 1967-1969 (Box 540)
      - Miscellany, 1966-1970
      - Old Dominion University, Norfolk, Va., 1967-1970, (2 folders)
      - Reimbursements, 1967-1970
      - University of North Carolina, 1967-1970
        - Chapel Hill, N.C.
        - Charlotte, N.C.
      - University of Richmond, Richmond, Va., 1968-1970, (1 folder) (Box 541)
      - University of Virginia, Charlottesville, Va., 1967-1970
      - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, Blacksburg, Va., 1968-1970, (2 folders)
      - Wake Forest University, Winston-Salem, N.C., 1968-1969
      - Western Carolina University, Cullowhee, N.C., 1968-1970
  - American Catholic Conference, 1965-1972, (3 folders)
  - American Circle for the Reform Club See Container 662, Reform Club, London, England
  - American Council on Germany
    - 1983
    - 1984-1987, (8 folders) (Box 542)
    - 1988-2000, (3 folders) (Box 543)
  - American Enterprise Institute, 1985-1999, (3 folders)
  - American Family Business Institute, 2006
  - American Friends of the London School of Economics, 1980-1983
  - American Legislative Exchange Council (Box 544)
    - General, 1976-1984, 1996, (7 folders)
    - Legal cases, 1976, (2 folders)
  - American Literary Society, 1981-1983 (Box 545)
  - American Political Channel, 1993-1994
  - American Political Foundation, 1982-1984
  - Americans for Oxford, 1987
  - America's Future Foundation, 1999-2001
  - Bohemian Club, San Francisco, Calif., and Bohemian Grove
    - 1979, 1987-1991, (5 folders)
    - 1992-2011, (4 folders) (Box 546)
  - Bryce Harlow Foundation
    - General, 1989-1996, (2 folders)
    - Scholarship applications, 1991, (2 folders)
  - Capital Research Center, 1985-1996, (3 folders) (Box 547)
  - Capitol Data, 1976-1977, (3 folders)
  - Capitol Hill Club, Washington, D.C., 1970-1975
  - Capitol Research Corp.
    - Correspondence and memoranda, 1971-1972
    - Financial records, 1972
    - Miscellany, 1972
    - Newsletters, 1972, (2 folders) (Box 548)
    - Potential subscribers, 1972
    - Prospectus, 1972
    - Subscribers, 1972, (2 folders)
  - Carlucci Commission on Foreign Aid See Containers 567-572, Commission on Security and Economic Assistance
  - Catholic Advisory Committee for the 50th American Presidential Inaugural, 1984-1985
  - Catholic Economic Association
    - 1965-1969, (4 folders)
    - 1970-1972, (2 folders) (Box 549)
  - Center for Applied Economic Research, undated
  - Center for Education and Research in Free Enterprise, Texas Agricultural and Mechanical University, College Station, Tex.
    - 1981-1988, (5 folders)
    - 1989-1993, (4 folders) (Box 550)
  - Center for Security Policy, 1988-1989, 1996-1997, (4 folders)
  - Chatham Institute See Containers 518-519, Adam Smith Institute
  - Citizens for America (Box 551)
    - General
      - 1983-1985, (7 folders)
      - 1986, (4 folders) (Box 552)
      - 1987, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box 553)
      - 1988
      - 1989-1992
    - Miscellany, circa 1986
    - Newspaper clippings, 1984-1988, (3 folders)
  - Clare Boothe Luce Program of the Henry Luce Foundation (Box 554)
    - Committee meetings
      - 1989-1998, (10 folders)
      - 1999-2001, (8 folders) (Box 555)
      - 2002-2003, (6 folders) (Box 556)
      - 2004, (1 folder) (Box 557)
      - 2005-2007, (6 folders)
      - 2008-2013, (10 folders) (Box 558)
      - 2014, (4 folders) (Box 559)
    - General
      - 1987-1988, (2 folders)
      - 1989, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 560)
      - 1990-2001, (6 folders)
      - 2003-2013, (2 folders) (Box 561)
    - Grant lists, 1989-2002, (4 folders)
    - Invited institutions, 1991-2008, (3 folders) (Box 562)
    - Miscellany, 1987-2005, (2 folders)
    - Proposals
      - 1989-1991, (3 folders)
      - 1992, (6 folders) (Box 563)
      - 1993-1994, (6 folders) (Box 564)
      - 1995-2000, (7 folders) (Box 565)
      - 2002-2003, 2014, (3 folders) (Box 566)
    - Reports, 1990-2010, (5 folders)
  - Claremont Institute, Advisory Board for the Lincoln Fellows Program, 1988-1999 (Box 567)
  - Club for Growth, Washington, D.C., 1999-2000
  - Commission on Security and Economic Assistance
    - Commission meetings, 1983
      - May-July, (7 folders)
      - Sept-Nov., (4 folders) (Box 568)
    - Correspondence and memoranda, 1983
      - Mar.-Sept., (3 folders)
      - Oct.-Nov., (2 folders) (Box 569)
    - Economic Assistance Fund Task Force, 1983, (2 folders)
    - Final report, drafts, 1983, (3 folders); (2 folders) (Box 570)
    - Military Assistance Task Force, 1983, (2 folders)
    - Miscellany, 1983
      - Commission creation, (2 folders)
      - Rickerson, Bruce (Box 571)
      - Staff résumés
    - Newspaper clippings, 1981-1983
    - Notes, 1983
    - Public hearings, 1983, (4 folders)
    - Research, 1983, (5 folders) (Box 572)
  - Congressional Commission on International Financial Institutions See Containers 629-632, International Financial Institution Advisory Commission
  - Congressional Policy Advisory Board, 1998-2000
  - Conservative Caucus, Citizens Cabinet Organizing Committee, 1977-1983
  - Council for National Policy (Box 573)
    - Executive Committee meetings
      - 1987-1990, (6 folders)
      - 1991-1993, (6 folders) (Box 574)
      - 1994-1998, (5 folders) (Box 575)
      - 1999-2001, (3 folders) (Box 576)
    - General
      - 1984-1986, (3 folders)
      - 1987, (1 folder) (Box 577)
      - 1988-1992, (8 folders)
      - 1993-1996, (6 folders) (Box 578)
      - 1997, (1 folder) (Box 579)
      - 1998-2001, (7 folders)
      - 2006-2012 (Box 580)
    - Miscellany, 1993, 2002, 2009, (2 folders)
  - Credit International Bank See also Containers 699-705, Sequoia National Bank
    - Auditing and Examining Committee
      - 1989-1991, (5 folders)
      - 1992-1993, (2 folders) (Box 581)
    - Board meetings
      - 1987-1989, (6 folders)
      - 1990-1993, (6 folders) (Box 582)
    - Capital plan, 1992-1993, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 583)
    - Financial records, 1988-1993, (2 folders)
    - General
      - 1986-1988, (3 folders)
      - 1989, (1 folder) (Box 584)
      - 1990-1992, (7 folders)
      - 1993, (2 folders) (Box 585)
    - Incorporation, 1986-1990, (3 folders)
    - Legal cases
      - Credit International Bank v. Lucey, 1990
      - El-Alfi v. Credit International Bancshares, 1991
      - Fineberg v. Credit International Bancshares, 1993-1994, (3 folders) (Box 586)
    - Loans, 1987-1993
    - Mergers
      - Federal Capital Bank, 1992
      - John Hanson Savings Bank, 1990, (1 folder) (Box 587)
      - Sequoia Federal Savings Bank, 1993, (4 folders)
    - Miscellany, circa 1987
    - Prospective investors, 1987-1989, (3 folders) (Box 588)
    - Reports
      - Board presentation, 1990
      - Criticized asset report, 1992
      - Internal assessment, 1992, (2 folders)
      - Management assessment, 1992 (Box 589)
      - Operating plan, 1987
      - Report of examination, 1991
      - Strategic plan, 1992
    - Shareholders, 1988-1991, (2 folders)
  - East Side Conservative Club of New York, New York, N.Y., 1985
  - Empower America, 1993-2001, (2 folders) (Box 590)
  - Equestrian Order of the Holy Sepulchre of Jerusalem, 1999-2010, (2 folders)
  - European Democratic Union, 1994-1995 See also Containers 628-629, International Democratic Union; Container 649, Pacific Democratic Union
  - First Friday Group, 1985-1986, (2 folders) (Box 591)
  - Foundation Francisco Marroquin
    - 1981-1987, (6 folders)
    - 1988-1996, (4 folders) (Box 592)
  - Foundation of the German-American Tricentennial Commission See Container 661, President's Commission for the German-American Tricentennial
  - Frank S. Meyer Society, 1993-1998
  - Fund for Living American Government, 1984-1992
  - George Mason University, Fairfax, Va.
    - Board of Visitors
      - Manual, 1998-2003, (3 folders); (2 folders) (Box 593)
      - Meetings
        - 1996-1997, (4 folders)
        - 1998, (1 folder) (Box 594)
        - 1999-2000, (4 folders)
        - 2001, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box 595)
        - 2002, (3 folders)
        - 2003, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 596)
        - 2004, (2 folders)
    - Financial records, 1996-2002, (3 folders)
    - General
      - 1996, (1 folder) (Box 597)
      - 1997-1999, (6 folders)
      - 2000, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 598)
      - 2001-2004, (5 folders)
    - Miscellany (Box 599)
      - Construction projects, 1996
      - Fact books, 1995-2003, (2 folders)
      - Institute for Humane Studies, 2012
      - Meese, Edwin, portrait, 2004-2005
      - Presidential evaluations, 2001-2003, (2 folders)
    - New Century College, 1997-1999, (5 folders); (2 folders) (Box 600, Box 601)
  - Hayek Institute, 2012
  - Hegeler Institute, 1975-1978
  - Hong Kong Policy Research Institute, Hong Kong (China), 1999
  - Hoover Institution on War, Revolution and Peace, 1972-1995, (4 folders)
  - House Administrative Assistants Alumni Association, 1996
  - Hudson Institute, 1984-1994, (1 folder) (Box 602)
  - Institut d'Etudes Politiques
    - 1985-1991, (9 folders)
    - 1992-1996, (9 folders) (Box 603)
    - 1997-2003, (8 folders) (Box 604)
    - 2004-2010, (9 folders) (Box 605)
    - 2011 (Box 606)
  - Institute for Corean-American Studies, 1997-2001, (2 folders)
  - Institute for Educational Affairs
    - 1986-1987, (3 folders)
    - 1988-1990, (6 folders) (Box 607)
  - Institute for European Defence & Strategic Studies
    - General
      - 1978
      - 1979-1986, (9 folders) (Box 608)
      - 1987-1991, (9 folders) (Box 609)
      - 1992-1998, undated, (8 folders) (Box 610)
    - Newspaper clippings
      - 1979-1984, (2 folders)
      - 1985-1993, (4 folders) (Box 611)
    - Tax files
      - 1989-1993, (6 folders)
      - 1994-1996, (6 folders) (Box 612)
  - Institute for Research on the Economics of Taxation (Box 613)
    - 1979-1987, (8 folders)
    - 1988, (2 folders)
  - Intercollegiate Society of Individualists See Containers 614-627, Intercollegiate Studies Institute (Box 614)
  - Intercollegiate Studies Institute
    - Board of Trustees meetings
      - 1979-1988, (8 folders)
      - 1989-1992, (7 folders) (Box 615)
      - 1993-1996, (7 folders) (Box 616)
      - 1997, (1 folder) (Box 617)
      - 1998-2001, (6 folders)
      - 2002-2006, (7 folders) (Box 618)
      - 2007-2014, (6 folders) (Box 619)
    - General
      - 1963-1978, (4 folders)
      - 1979-1984, (9 folders) (Box 620)
      - 1985-1989, (8 folders) (Box 621)
      - 1990-1991, (7 folders) (Box 622)
      - 1992, (1 folder) (Box 623)
      - 1993-1995, (7 folders)
      - 1996-1999, (8 folders) (Box 624)
      - 2000-2006, (7 folders) (Box 625)
      - 2007-2013, (7 folders) (Box 626)
      - 2014 (Box 627)
    - Miscellany
      - Alumni book, undated
      - Evaluation Committee, 1987, (3 folders)
      - Intercollegiate Review, 1967-1972
      - Western Summer Seminar, Los Angeles, Calif., 1969, (3 folders)
  - International Center for Economic Policy Studies See Containers 636-637, Manhattan Institute of Policy Studies
  - International Cooperation Organization, 1986-1986 (Box 628)
  - International Democratic Union See also Container 590, European Democratic Union; Container 649, Pacific Democratic Union
    - 1993-1994 (4 folders
    - 1995, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 629)
    - 1996-1999
  - International Freedom Academy See Container 661, same heading
  - International Financial Institution Advisory Commission
    - Commission findings, 2000
    - General, 1999-2000
    - Meeting material
      - 1999
        - Aug.
        - Sept., (1 folder) (Box 630)
        - Oct.-Dec., (5 folders)
      - 2000, Jan.
    - Meetings, 1999, (2 folders) (Box 631)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1999-2000
    - Research, 1998-1999, (3 folders) (Box 632)
  - International Institute for Strategic Studies, 1975-1976
  - International Policy Forum, 1982-1983, (2 folders)
  - International Republican Institute
    - 1994
    - 1995-2001, (5 folders) (Box 633)
  - Invisible Hand Society, 1964-1975
  - John F. Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts, Washington, D.C., 1989-1991
  - John Templeton Foundation, 1993-1998, (3 folders) (Box 634)
  - Joseph Story Society, 1987
  - Kemp Commission See Containers 640-648, National Commission on Economic Growth and Tax Reform
  - Kingston Group
    - 1973-1974, (3 folders)
    - 1975-1977, undated, (2 folders) (Box 635)
  - Knights of Malta See Container 706, Sovereign Military Order of Malta
  - Lehrman Institute, 1981-1992, (3 folders)
  - Liberty Foundation of America, 2013-2014, (1 folder) (Box 636)
  - London House, London, England, 1966-1968
  - Lynde and Harry Bradley Foundation, 2003-2013, (2 folders)
  - Manhattan Institute of Policy Studies
    - 1976-1980, (2 folders)
    - 1981-1985, (5 folders) (Box 637)
  - Meltzer Commission See Containers 629-632, International Financial Institution Advisory Commission
  - Mentor Group, 1983-1989 See also Containers 138-144, administrative memoranda
  - Metropolitan Club of the City of Washington, Washington, D.C., 1981-2013, (5 folders) (Box 638)
  - Mobilization Concepts Development Center Distinguished Fellows, 1984-1987, (4 folders) (Box 639)
  - Mont Pelerin Society, 1968, 1972-1973, 1988-1989, 1996-1998, 2004, 2010-2014
  - National Center for Public Policy Research, 1986-1992
  - National Chamber Foundation, 1997-2010, (3 folders) (Box 640)
  - National Commission on Economic Growth and Tax Reform
    - Financial records, 1995-1997, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box 641)
    - General, 1995-1996, (3 folders)
    - Miscellany
      - Newspaper clippings, 1995-1996
      - Notes, 1995-1996
      - Public relations, 1995-1996, (2 folders) (Box 642)
      - Surveys, 1995
      - Website, 1996
    - Planning binders
      - 1995
        - May-June, (3 folders)
        - Aug., (1 folder); (4 folders) (Box 643)
        - Oct.
          - 10, (1 folder) (Box 644)
          - 11, (5 folders)
          - 20 (Box 645)
        - Nov.
          - 3-14, (5 folders)
          - 16 (Box 646)
        - Dec., (5 folders)
      - 1996, Mar.